Okay, we're going to add a nice Medjool date. These are beautiful dates, wow. They're so sweet and really soft. I find that, from my own personal experience, that when I buy things in volume and I'm not a very small little business here, and so I don't buy volume very often, but I have bought dates in volume.
They just don't seem to have the same flavor as when I buy just a handful of them at my favorite health market.
So, that's kind of one of the reasons the expense seems to be so high.
There's a supplier for the restaurants, and I will not mention them, and they supply almost every restaurant I've ever been in the back room and I find this company name and it's just not quality.
You can taste it, and wherever they've cut corners where they could, they did.
You can taste the difference.
It's funny, we care so much more about our cars then our bodies.
You can switch out a car and buy a new car every four years, I think the average is, and this is the one body I get for this experience, this life, this is it and so why we don't take more time in choosing what we want to put in it, it surprises me.
I'm talking about myself as well.
I'm going to try and think a little bit more, stay a little more present, do a little more research before we just put the hamburger in our stomachs, and then we don't feel good the rest of the day and we can't figure out why.
Everyone that I've introduced raw foods to, they say the same thing.
They can't believe that that raw food could taste like this.
I think that they just thought that it was going to be an apple or something.
Nothing wrong with an apple, but as you can see, there's lots more we can do.